[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who invented the armonica, a musical instrument made up of a series of tuned spinning  bowls?", "correct_answer": "Benjamin Franklin", "incorrect_answers": ["Sir Edward Elgar", "Dean Shostak", "Thomas Edison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1976 film was honored with the Oscar for Best Picture at the 49th Academy Awards ceremony in 1977.", "correct_answer": "Rocky", "incorrect_answers": ["Taxi Driver", "Network", "Bound for Glory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Mahjong, a pong is a set of how many identical tiles?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "6", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What condition is characterized by fear of men?", "correct_answer": "Hominophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Hormephobia", "Homichlophobia", "Hodophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The medical prefix oophoro, which derives from Greek, refers to which part of the body?", "correct_answer": "Ovary", "incorrect_answers": ["Muscle", "Uterus", "Abdomen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1981 Italian film was set in New Orleans at the Seven Doors Hotel which was supposedly built over the gates of hell.", "correct_answer": "The Beyond", "incorrect_answers": ["Poltergeist", "Suspiria", "The House By The Cemetery"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times was the phrase \u201dIt\u2019s good to be the king said in the movie History of the World, Part I?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "6", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was the 11 Oscar nominated movie The Color Purple released?", "correct_answer": "1985", "incorrect_answers": ["1983", "1984", "1980"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the Greek word Embioptera, which denotes an order of insects, also known as webspinners?", "correct_answer": "Lively wings", "incorrect_answers": ["Small wings", "None of these", "Yarn knitter"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 2004 Indian Ocean earthquake was an undersea earthquake that generated a tsunami, which claimed the lives of more than 150,000 people (this is true). The earthquake lasted nearly ten minutes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where shouldnt unmarried people sit if they dont want to stay single for a long time according to Russian superstition?", "correct_answer": "At the corner of the table", "incorrect_answers": ["At a crossroad", "Under the table", "Under an oak tree"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many compartments are in a cows stomach?", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["6", "5", "3"]}]